Casey Murrow Collection of Edward R. Murrow Materials MS255
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Professional papers, 1920 -- 2002; MS255.000087
  - Israel trip, P.M. Ben-Gurion, circa 1950 -- 1959; MS255.000145; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Freedom House award and event program, 1954; MS255.000146; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Malaria Eradication Commemorative U.S. Postage Stamp, 1962; MS255.000147; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Park dedication DC, 1979; MS255.000148; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Edward R. Murrow 1943 pocket calendar and CBS ID card, MS255.000149; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ed bio in Janet's handwriting, circa 1965; MS255.000150; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, circa 1940 -- 1988; MS255.000151; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Telegrams to Edward R. Murrow, 1938 -- 1943; MS255.000152; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - World War II-era passes and ID, circa 1943; MS255.000153; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Edward R. Murrow Park dedication, 1979 April; MS255.000154; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Presentation of tray to Naval Museum photographs, 1974; MS255.000155; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Joe Persico biography of Edward R. Murrow, circa 1920 -- 1985; MS255.000156; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - William S. Paley and Janet Murrow photograph, circa 1970 -- 1979; MS255.000157; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Conflicts of interest correspondence, 1962 -- 1963; MS255.000158; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Edward R. Murrow High School correspondence and clippings, circa 1974; MS255.000159; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "Reflections on Ed Murrow" drafts and correspondence, 1978 -- 1980; MS255.000160; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Joseph Wershba correspondence, 1979 -- 1984; MS255.000161; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - "In Search of Light" royalty, 1966 -- 1980; MS255.000162; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Murrow's McCarthy broadcast anniversary clippings and correspondence, 1979; MS255.000163; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - "In Search of Light" correspondence, 1966 -- 1968; MS255.000164; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Scripts, 1954 -- 1968; MS255.000165; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Reviews - Prime Time, 1969; MS255.000166; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1953 -- 1979; MS255.000167; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Murrow press clippings, 1953 -- 1979; MS255.000168; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Edward R. Murrow material sent to James Seward, 1941 -- 1967; MS255.000169; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Leo Deorsey, 1958 -- 1963; MS255.000170; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Person to Person contracts and correspondence, 1956 -- 1962; MS255.000171; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sarah and Alex Kendrick correspondence, 1979 -- 1982; MS255.000172; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Edward R. Murrow film project, 1978 -- 1981; MS255.000173; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "End of Fear" book chapter by Edward Bliss, Jr., 1984; MS255.000174; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Murrow: A One-Character Play in Tow Acts" by Bill Brown and Ed Sharnik, circa 1975; MS255.000175; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Legal documents and correspondence, 1984; MS255.000176; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - James M. Seward correspondence, 1985 -- 1986; MS255.000177; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ERM album #2 drafts and correspondence, 1965 -- 1968; MS255.000178; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Murrow retrospective, 1972 January; MS255.000179; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Edward R. Murrow -- Jefferson Productions, 1957 -- 1973; MS255.000180; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Contract duplicates, 1947 -- 1961; MS255.000181; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Murrow, Edward R. basic employment agreements, 1960; MS255.000182; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Murrow biography, 1966; MS255.000183; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Edward R. Murrow employment and royalties agreements, circa 1935 -- 1964; MS255.000184; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Murrow, Edward R. - Jefferson Productions, Inc. - McGraw Hill Book Company, Inc. (See It Now - film syndication), 1956 -- 1957; MS255.000185; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jefferson - Corp Trust Co, circa 1969 -- 1971; MS255.000186; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson Productions, Inc. corporate records, circa 1954 -- 1967; MS255.000187; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Edward R. Murrow Memorial Fund Overseas Press Club Foundation photographs, 1966; MS255.000188; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Box 3)
  - Edward R. and Janet Murrow photographs, circa 1941 -- 1960; MS255.000189; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Look magazine cover and clipping, 1959; MS255.000190; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Tufts Murrow Center of Public Diplomacy dedication photograph, 1965; MS255.000191; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - David Ben-Gurion photograph, circa 1955; MS255.000192; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Edward R. Murrow and President Johnson photograph, 1963; MS255.000193; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6)
- 2022 accessions, 1791, 1946; MS255.000194; 1 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  This series contains a two-volume first edition of "The Life of Samuel Johnson, LL.D" by James Boswell, as well as a letter from Howard K. Smith to Edward R. Murrow upon his departure from CBS. The volumes date to 1791 and the correspondence from 1946. The volumes were gifted to Edward R. Murrow by Howard K. Smith, Murrow's successor as London Bureau Chief for CBS.
  - Letter to Edward R. Murrow from Howard K. Smith, 1946; MS255.000195 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The Life of Samuel Johnson, LL.D, volume I, 1791; MS255.000196; 1 Volumes (Box 9)
    Gift of Casey R. Murrow, 2022, accession MS-2023-043.
  - The Life of Samuel Johnson, LL.D, volume II, 1791; MS255.000197; 1 Volumes (Box 10)
    Gift of Casey Murrow, 2022, accession MS-2023-043.